O'kay so that application is out and now you're thinking classes.
Where do I take classes?
There is a barrage of places that you can take real estate classes.
You can take them on line, you can take them at your local community college, or you can take them at a local real estate school.
You might live in a small town and you're thinking real estate school?
Where's the closest one?
Well it might be 45 minutes away.
Well let me tell you now and this is based on my experience.
There is thousands of realtors in the world.
They all have their own experience and I feel that I'm one of the best out there though because of my research in finding a good school and that kind of thing so let me tell you how to do it.
When you're thinking about a great school, call, you've seen that guy whatever his name is or gal and she's all over the signs like me, Shelly Davis, you know everywhere you turn you see Shelly Davis' team, Shelly Davis, pick up the phone and call Shelly Davis and say where did you go to school, what worked for you?
There is always going to be a real estate school that has a stellar reputation amongst the realtors and there's a reason why.